Johnson, Lawrence R. Missouri Pacific Railroad and Railroad Union Publications 6330 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lawrence R. Johnson Missouri Pacific Railroad and Railroad Union Publications
1939-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Johnson, Lawrence R.
Missouri Pacific Railroad (MOPAC)
Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT)
Order of Railway Conductors (ORC)
United Transportation Union (UTU)
6330 PUBS
2.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Publications.
7541352
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 27, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions; Johnson, Lawrence R.; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Missouri Pacific Railroad Company; United Transportation Union
7541352
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and United Transportation Union (Box 1)
  - Cliff Merritt (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Cliff Merritt's Scrapbook of Man on the Move, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Language: English.
    - Item 2: Cliff Merritt's Scrapbook People on the Move, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 3: Cliff Merritt's Scrapbook "People on the Move", Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 4: Cliff Merritt's Scrapbook "People on the Move!", Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 5: Cliff Merritt and the Very Candid Candidate, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 6: People who Move the Nation by Cliff Merritt An Educational Book for Children, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Author: Cliff Merritt
      Format: Publication
    - Item 7: People who Move the Nation by Cliff Merritt An Educational Book For Children, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 8: The Cliff Merritt Railroad Coloring Book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - BRT. Constitutions 1946-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Isurance Department, 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 2: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Insurance Department, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 3: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Insurance Department, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - BRT. Directory 1963, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Directory of the Grand Lodge and Subordinate Lodges, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - BRT. General, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: An Outline of the Procedural Requirements in Handling Disputes Under the Railway Labor Act, Including Disciplinary Matters, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 2: Railroads in the United States, Canada and Alaska on which the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Holds the Contract for Yardsmen and Yardmasters, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 3: Railroads in the United States Canada and Alaska on Which the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Holds the Contract for Road Conductors, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 4: Railroads in the United States and Canada on which the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Holds the Contract for Dining Car Stewards, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 5: Financial Statement, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 6: A Brief Sketch of Its History, Functions and Accomplishments, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 7: Financial Statement By Departments, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 8: Financial Statement, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 9: Your Labor Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 10: Milestones and Roadblocks in Labor's Progress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 11: Principles Governing Interchange Movements Between Carriers as Applied by Awards of the First Division, National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 12: Conductors Facts You Should Know About the Agreement to Amalgamate the ORC&B and BRT, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 13: Misleaders of Railroad Labor or "Of Mice and Men", 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - BRT. Insurance 1939-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Accident and Health Hospital and Surgical, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - BRT. Joint Benefit Fund 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Rules and Regulations of the Job Benefit Fund, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 2: Rules and Regulations of the Job Benefit Fund, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 3: Rules and Regulations of the Job Benefit Fund, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - BRT. Ladies Auxiliary 1963-1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Constitution and General Rules, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 2: Revisions and Additions to the Constitution of the Ladies Auxiliary to the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainsmen, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 3: Constitution and General Rules Ladies Auxiliary of the United Transportation Union, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - BRT. Manual of Information and Instruction 1962, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Manual of Information and Instructions (Former Negotiating Manual, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - BRT. Negotiating Manual 1957, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Negotiating Manual, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - BRT. Our Fight for Democracy, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Our Fight for Democracy: The REAL Reasons Why President Kennedy Tried to Delay Our Convention, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Author: Clyde Titler
  - BRT. Relief and Compensation Fund 1973-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Brotherhood's Relief and Compensation Fund, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Item 2: Constitution of the Brotherhood's Relief and Compensation Fund, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - BRT. Report of the Board of Appeals 1944, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Report of the Board of Appeals, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - BRT. Ritual of Subordinate Lodges 1955, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Ritual of Subordinate Lodges of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - BRT. Strength of Brotherhood, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Strength in Brotherhood: The Story of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trianmen, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - BRT. Time Books 1946-1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: 1949-1950 Rime Book (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 2: Time Book, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - BRT. Trainmen News 1953-1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Trainsmen News, 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 2: Trainman News, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 3: Trainman News, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 4: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 5: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 6: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 7: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 8: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 9: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - BRT. Trainmen News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 2: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 3: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 4: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 5: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 6: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 7: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 8: Training News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 9: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 10: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 11: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 12: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 13: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 14: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 15: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 16: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 17: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 18: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 19: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 20: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 21: Trainman News, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 22: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 23: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 24: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 25: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 26: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 27: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 28: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 29: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 30: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 31: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 32: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 33: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 34: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 35: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 36: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 37: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 38: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 39: Trainman News, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - BRT. Unigram, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Unigram: Unification, Path to the Future, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - BRT. Your Labor Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Your Labor Union; A Brief Sketch of Its History, Functions and Accomplishments, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 2: Your Labor Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - UTU. Accounting Procedure and Instructional Manual, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Accounting Procedure and Instruction Manual for Board of Trustees and Treasurers of All Locals, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - UTU. Agreements 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Agreement Dated April 27, 1973 between Railroads Represented by the National Carriers' Conference Committee and their Employees Represented by the United Transportation Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 2: Agreement Dated April 27, 1973 between Railroads Represented by the National Carriers' Conference Committee, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 3: Mediation Agreement Case No. A-8830 Between Railroads Represented by National Railway Labor Conference and The Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees and Employees of suck Carriers Represented by the United Transportation Union, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 4: Meidation Agreement Case No. A-8830 Between Railroads Represented by National Railway Labor Conference and The Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees and Employees of Such Carriers Represented by the United Transportation Union, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 5: Mediation Agreement Case No. !-8830 Between Railroads Represented by National Railway Labor Conference and The Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - UTU. Basic Day and Seniority Rules 1969, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Basic Day and Seniority Rules, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - UTU Celebrating A Quarter Century 1994, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Celebrating A Quarter of a Century of Progress Through Unity, 1969-1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 2: Celebrating A Quarter of a Century of Progress Through Unity, 1969-1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - UTU. Constitutions 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Constitution, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 2: Constitution, 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 3: Constitution, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 4: Constitution, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - UTU. Construction and Interpretation of Agreements 1969, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Construction and Interpretation of Agreements, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - UTU. General, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Your Labor Union, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 2: What the Loss of 100 Railroad Jobs Means to Communities Across the United States, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 3: Your Labor Union, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 4: 20 Questions and Answers on TPEL, 1981; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 5: How it Serves You, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 6: Safety Rules, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 7: How it Serves You, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 8: Operation Red Block, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - UTU. Getting a Message to Congress 1993, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Getting a Message to Congress, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 2: How to Protect your Rights when Injured on the Job, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 3: Railroad Related Injuries, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - UTU. How to Protect Your Rights when Injured on the Job, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Injured Railroad Workers Know Your Rights, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - UTU. The Injured Man 1969, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: The Injured Man, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - UTU. Insurance, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Performance Report, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Item 2: 1994 Regional Meeting Hot Springs, Arkansas, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Item 3: Group Health Insurance Plans, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - UTU. Mainliner 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: General Committee of Adjustment Missouri Pacific (Proper), 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Author: Irving Newcomb
    - Item 2: General Committee of Adjustment Missouri Pacific (Proper) December 1976, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 3: Newsletter, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 4: Newsletter, 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 5: Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 6: Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 7: Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 8: Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - UTU. Newsletter 1975, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 2: Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - UTU. People Helping People 1993, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: People Helping, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - UTU. Proceedings of the Second Convention 1975, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: "Progress Through Unity", 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 2: "Progress Through Unity", 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 3: "Progress through Unity", 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 4: "Prgoress Through Unity", 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 5: "Progress Through Unity", 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Item 6: "Progress Through Unity", 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - UTU. Railroad Investigating and Discipline 1969, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: Railroad Investigations and Discipline, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - UTU. Rate Tables from Agreement 1975, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Rate Tables from Agreement, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - UTU. Report of the Committee on Constitution 1975, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Report on the Committee on Constitution Second Convention, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - UTU. Safety Appliance Acts, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: The Safety Appliance Acts Interstate Commerce Commission, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 2: The Safety Appliance Acts Interstate Commerce Commission, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - UTU. Supplement to Constitution, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Supplement to Constitution, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - UTU. Timebooks 1973-1991 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Member's Time Book, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Item 2: 1973 Time Book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - UTU. News 1978, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: UTU News, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - UTU Transportation News 1970, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 2: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 3: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 4: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 5: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 6: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 7: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 8: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 9: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 10: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 11: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 12: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 13: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 14: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 15: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 16: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 17: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 18: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 19: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 20: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 21: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 22: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 23: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 24: Transportaiton News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 25: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 26: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 27: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 28: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 29: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 30: Transportation News, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
- United Transportation Union, Other Unions, and Missouri Pacific Railroad, Publication (Box 2)
  - UTU Transportation News 1971, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 2: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 3: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 4: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 5: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 6: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 7: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 8: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 9: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 10: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 11: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 12: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 13: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 14: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 15: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 16: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 17: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 18: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 19: Transportion News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 20: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 21: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 22: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 23: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 24: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 25: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 26: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 27: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 28: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 29: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 30: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 31: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 32: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 33: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 34: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 35: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 36: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 37: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 38: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 39: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 40: Transportation News, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - UTU Transportation News 1972, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Transportation News, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairmen, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairmen, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - UTU Unification Agreement and Constitution, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Unification Agreement and Constitution, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Item 2: Unification Agreement and Constitution, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - UTU The Unity Move In Railroad Labor 1968, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: The Unity Move in Railroad Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - UTU. Voting Instructions 2002, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Voting Instructions, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - UTU. Washington Report 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Washington Report, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - BLE. Locomotion Engineer 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Locomotive Engineer, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Item 2: Locomotive Engineer, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Item 3: Locomotive Engineer, 1973; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - BLF&E Ritual of B of LF & E 1945, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)